<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lukayeh</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on lukayeh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Terragrunt</title>
      <link>/posts/getting-started-with-terragrunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/getting-started-with-terragrunt/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This blog post is going to cover my initial journey into Terragrunt and deploying a simple S3 Bucket to AWS as per my previous examples as this is the simplest way to play with Terraform/grunt/whatever
Lets DO IT Prerequisites As this tutorial utilises AWS make sure you have setup a AWS account and ran aws configure with the correct credentials, this page is helpful for this kinda thing:
https://www.cyberciti.biz/faq/osx-installing-the-aws-command-line-interface-using-brew/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Terraform Workspaces to manage multi-env deployments</title>
      <link>/posts/terraform-workspaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/terraform-workspaces/</guid>
      <description>Using Terraform Workspaces to manage multi-env deployments Hi! This blog post will cover working with Terraform Workspaces that allow you to manage multiple enviroments under the same code, this is one of many ways to do this with terraform (see using --var-file=development.tfvars) and I was interested in figuring out how this would work, I can&amp;rsquo;t say it&amp;rsquo;s the right way but I can say it&amp;rsquo;s fairly straight forward however I have yet to use this at a large scale, so lets have a plan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/posts/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Place holder for a about me !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dockerizing a Hugo Site</title>
      <link>/posts/dockerize-a-hugo-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dockerize-a-hugo-site/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Alright I lied, I&amp;rsquo;ll do another blog post, seeing as you all asked so nicely! This post expands upon starting-a-hugo-site and will show you have to package up HUGO in docker, I mean sure you can just upload it to S3 in AWS and run as a static page, but if you&amp;rsquo;re like me you want to mess around with shiny things and I guess Docker is shiny?
Getting Started Install Docker Homebrew is a package manager for macOS, can be installed from brew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a Hugo Site</title>
      <link>/posts/starting-a-hugo-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/starting-a-hugo-site/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hi! this is going to be my first blog post here, and it&amp;rsquo;s going to pretty much run through how I generated it in the first Hazzar I hear you say.
If you want to skip this and get the quick start on how to get HUGO up and running go ahead and read this document here from Hugos standard documentation or you can read my blog?
Just as a headsup I&amp;rsquo;m running on a MacBook Pro (15-inch, 2018), so this post atleast is tailored to MacOS if you need assistance with Windows then&amp;hellip;well figure it out Getting Started Install Hugo Homebrew is a package manager for macOS, can be installed from brew.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
